Hartel, Lois Papers 6247
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lois Hartel Papers
1969-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hartel, Lois
6247
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers.
6191385
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 6247 P: Lois Hartel Photographs
Hartel, Lois
6191385
- UNITE Chorus 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- United Way, Mobilizing America, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Time Study Workshop for Union Officers 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Summer School for Union Women (NE region), 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Labor - Management Committee tribute + awards luncheon, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Delores, Tucker 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Milrite Council, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Union Cards, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Von Realte, Inc. + Dunkirk, Inc. v. ILGWU et al. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "We Are All Equal" 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Local 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Local 10, 1969-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ILGWU/ACTWU, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1997 Executive Board Meeting Minutes & Communities, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- United Way, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Local 1, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- U.S. Congress, State Senate of Pennsylvania & United Way, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Union News, 1994-2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Awards + Tributes, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- United Way, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Clippings and Photographs, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)